var questions = [
    {
        "question" : "1 - Who is SpongeBob's best friend?",
        "ans1": "Gary",
        "ans2": "Karen",
        "ans3": "Patrick Star",
        "ans4": "Sandy Cheeks",
        "ans": "3"
    },
    {
        "question" : "2 - What do SpongeBob and Patrick name their bivalve?",
        "ans1": "Junior",
        "ans2": "Senior",
        "ans3": "Star",
        "ans4": "Candy",
        "ans": "1"
    },
    {
        "question" : "3 - In the episode SpongeBob Meets the Strangler, how much does the mustache the Strangler wears cost?",
        "ans1": "two cents",
        "ans2": "three cents",
        "ans3": "four cents",
        "ans4": "five cents",
        "ans": "4"
    },
    {
        "question" : "4 - Three of the following quotes are Mermaid Man quotes. One is not. Which is not?",
        "ans1": "Stop shoutin' I'm nappin",
        "ans2": "EVIL",
        "ans3": "Up, up and away",
        "ans4": "I think you overcooked this a little.",
        "ans": "4"
    },
    {
        "question" : "5 - What was the name of the Krusty Krab before Mr. Krabs bought it?",
        "ans1": "Karen",
        "ans2": "Nusty Krab",
        "ans3": "Rusty Krab",
        "ans4": "Mr.B",
        "ans": "3"
    },
    {
        "question" : "6 - Which of the following episodes does Mr. Krabs never appear in?",
        "ans1": "Ghoul Fools",
        "ans2": "A Day Without Tears",
        "ans3": "PreHibernation Week ",
        "ans4": "You Don't Know Sponge",
        "ans": "4"
    },
    {
        "question" : "7 - What is the only episode where Larry the Lobster is referred to as Big Larry?",
        "ans1": "Ghoul Fools",
        "ans2": "Ripped Pants",
        "ans3": "PreHibernation Week ",
        "ans4": "You Don't Know Sponge",
        "ans": "2"
    },
    {
        "question" : "8 - In the episode Ditchin, SpongeBob ditches school with the help of Patrick. Which of the following excuses is the correct one?",
        "ans1": "He didn't go to the toilet until tomorrow",
        "ans2": "He has diarrhea",
        "ans3": "He has to feed Gary",
        "ans4": "He wanted to get hishomework",
        "ans": "1"
    },
    {
        "question" : "9 - In SB-129, how many letters does Sponge-Tron say there are in the alphabet?",
        "ans1": "486",
        "ans2": "488",
        "ans3": "386",
        "ans4": "345",
        "ans": "1"
    },
    {
        "question" : "10 - Often when Patrick is laughing really crazy or saying/doing something really dumb, how many upper teeth is he shown to have?",
        "ans1": "One",
        "ans2": "Two",
        "ans3": "Three",
        "ans4": "None",
        "ans": "1"
    }
    


];

